Okay, so welcome ladies. I don't think this is going to be a super long call,
but it
was just something that we were talking about recently. Well, I was talking
about with Chloe
and realised just she's got so many good tips and so much to say about love and
I was like,
this would be a great call and just a great thing to have on our website that
we can direct people
to as well if they want some inspiration around it or a few tips and things. So
it's only a few
slides. I'm just going to talk through the slides and then I'll come to you,
Chloe,
back and forth as we go through because it is Chloe that is the expert on love
and not me
by any means. So thank you so much Chloe for doing this and for helping and to,
yeah,
for giving us some amazing tips and stuff. Obviously, like for anyone watching
this back,
you know, there's a bit of guidance here about Lovense, but you can always
ask your mentor
as well. And you know, if you need any extra help, the stuff that we can send
you and we can
guide you and help you. So you don't need to do it all on your own, but
hopefully you'll get some
good, some good info from this call. So what we're going to cover is just
mentioning what love
ends is for anyone who's not aware and why it works. We'll talk a little bit
about setup and the
different settings and got a few sort of tips and tricks and then of course you
can ask any
questions if you've got any questions or if you want to share how it's been for
you or anything at
all to do with Lovense. So, so what is it? So Lovense is a brand of app
controlled sex toys
designed to be used remotely that you can link with your AdultWork profile to
use on
account with your clients. So there's different types, different types of toys.
There are great way to encourage clients to engage and to tip you to control
your toys.
So tip you to give you a buzz and it's helpful to get you to extend your cam
sessions for longer.
So obviously, they've got something, anything that can keep the clients in for
longer, you know,
is what we want, isn't it? They're great for models who are comfortable with
sexual play
on cam. Of course, that's not for everyone. So if you're looking into it and
you don't feel so
comfortable, obviously we would never say go beyond what you're comfortable
with. But it can be
a really great tool for people that are comfortable doing that on cam. And, you
know, Chloe, I think
you were saying it was like it can just be a good starting point for people who
are like
comfortable doing this sort of thing on cam, but not as comfortable with the
chatting and
they're like where to start and stuff kind of gives you an in, like to sort of
something to talk
about and connect with people over. So that is love it. So set up, so let's
talk a little bit
about set up. So we do have, we do have some guidance that we can send you,
which is on the
other work website. There's also loads of YouTube videos and things that you
can watch just to
talk you through the set up process. But actually, when you make an account on
the Lovence site and
out and follow the instructions, they, I had a look at the instructions and
they are pretty good.
So they do have videos and text or whatever way you learn best. They are quite
comprehensive
and quite easy to follow. One thing that, so I we said, which I thought was
really important,
was that if you're looking to buy a Lovence, if you're looking to invest in one
, it's best to buy
directly from Lovence. So obviously you may find them cheaper elsewhere because
it is a bit of an
investment, but there are some fake ones lying around. So yeah, you don't want
to put any money
into something and then not be able to set it up and it just not be the right
thing. So
probably best to go direct to Lovence, if you can. Of course, like if you, if
you do okay on cam and
you've got regulars, you know, encouraging them to tip you so that you can buy
one in the first
place, it's always a good idea. Or even putting it on your profile that you're
saving up for one.
So come and come with me so that I can buy Lovence. So there's the instructions
for setup via the
actual Lovence site and there's also some extra guidance on AdultWork to do
with Lovence integration.
So integrating your AdultWork with the Lovence. You can do that from the Loven
ce site as well,
but but these instructions are quite helpful. So we can send this to anyone who
wants it,
you know, afterwards or anyone that's watching the video, because there are a
couple of links
that I can send with it as well for you to have a look at.
So if it's worth having a little look at those, is it going to work? Can you
see that?
It's loading, I don't know. I don't know, it's just going to work. No.
Okay, never mind. Never mind. Yeah, I was going to just share with you some of
the integration,
but that's okay. We can send you a link to anyone that's interested.
Okay, so let's have a little look at some of the tips and tricks that our
lovely Chloe was talking
about. Well, this is one actually that I was thinking about, but I think it was
off the back
of a conversation we had, Chloe, which was about capitalizing on competition.
So I think this is a
good, this is, you know, I think for me, like I don't do a lot of, you know, I
much prefer to be
chatting one-on-one with someone than in a group chat. But if I am in a group
chat,
that's something that I like to do anyway, is to kind of like have them, have
them competing,
who's going to take me to private, or who's going to do this or that, or just
kind of
putting them off against each other a little bit. And I think that maybe Lov
ance can come into that
as well. Do you want to see about that? Yeah, so there's actually an option on
Lovance for the
clients. So they have like a remote control. So you set the settings on the
price, you can have it
as little or as much as you want. You can do multiple different prices as well.
So you can have one
set-in for one credit, and then you can have another set-in for a hundred. You
can set everything so
you can pick and choose. You can change this as often as you like as well. So
on busy a days,
you can keep it expensive on quieter days. You can make it a little bit cheaper
. So that's really
helpful, but they do have a really fun feature on it. That's a block. So say
you're in group or three,
and someone's tipping you to lose a once, and the toy is going off. Someone
else can block their
tips like for a minute, and then they tip you out. So you're getting their buzz
ers
instead, and they can see that. So then they're blocking theirs back, and
tipping it, and it can
become like a quite a fun, because it comes up for us who's tipping as well. So
we can interact and
be like, "Oh, thank you, Brian. That's the one that's going on." And then
someone will block
Brian's, and they'll be like, "Oh, thank you, James." And it's really fun. And
you really do
do do it as well. I probably haven't had Lovense. I've probably had about a
year
now, but I've come for about three and a half. It helps me massively, and I am
someone who does
already have regulars, and I've got quite a big clientele, I'd say, on adult
work now,
with people who have been coming to me for the full few years, and I've
probably made the most
money in the last year because of my Lovense that I have throughout the whole
thing. So it really
does help. Even people who have got clients and got regulars, it really does
still help. You can
have it at any point. You can have it in the beginning of your journey, or you
can have it at
the end of your journey, and you're still going to see massive benefits from it
. But that is a really
fun game. Also, put your in category. So online, you'll notice the pages. So
you can be on page one,
two, three, four, twenty. Depends on how many girls are online, but men can
kind of
type in what they want. So they can see everyone who's in free, and that takes
you to a different
category. So you could be on the first page, if you're in free, then Lovense
does that option
as well. So they can actually see everyone who has a toy connected. And if
there's not that many,
again, it boosts you a couple of pages, because if they're looking for everyone
who's got a toy,
and only 10 girls online, I've got toys, you're one of 10, rather than one in
100,
or one in like 500 most of the time, unless you bid an awesome tonight. So it
also puts you
in a separate category that boosts your profile as well. And it's something to
talk about within
your profile as well. So it helps you to count anyway, because the morning, so
you're having
your profile for the ones that do read it, it's just good to talk about
something else. So you can
even have a separate section like this is middle events. This is how we can
play together. This is
what we can do. So it really does help in terms of competition, like with all
the girls and the
actual men as well, it works both sides with competition. Yeah, that's so, that
's so interesting,
that's so great. And can you tell us, because we skipped a bit there, realised
at the end,
can you tell us a bit more about the settings, Chloe? Yeah, oh yeah. So I'll
see, I've got it up now,
because I was going to see if I can show you my sentence, if I just flip my
camera around,
although as if not, I can just explain it. But it looks quite fun. So I thought
it might be fun,
if I can flip my camera around and show you what I've got. So yeah, so, so you
can see.
So this is what it looks like. So, and you can change these and have as many as
you want as well.
So I've only got the one toy, so that's just lush. And I've put one to four
credits,
get them five seconds on a low vibration. And then I've got five to ten credits
,
gets 15 seconds of amazing vibration. And then obviously I just go higher and
higher.
This one, 16, not 30, is my highest, is my most popular one. That one, I got a
lot of ones in three,
but we can talk about the three sides in a minute, because that's on there, isn
't it? But this is
actually my highest one, this is the most popular one. They never go past 16. I
'm not sure why,
probably because it's the same, isn't it? And I haven't got another one at the
minute. I did as
more, but I reset it all just to play around with it. So I do normally have
more than just four.
But this is what you can do. And you can change the vibrations and stuff as
well. So these are
just normal buzzers, but there's fun ones. So one of them's called volcano, I
think. And another
one's called like tear bell, but they can see what it's actually what you've
got the cold and stuff.
So they like, I'm sending it a volcano vibration for 30 seconds. And I do have
long, well, I did
have longer ones on there as well, where it is actually buzzing for like a
minute or five minutes
and stuff, but for more money. But I've noticed that 16 is my most popular one.
And that's a lot
to get in a core, like even if they just do that once at 16 credits and they
don't, they normally
keep going because they want your reaction and it's mainly face as well. Like
you'd think that
they'd be like, Oh, like, I want to see it in. I want it most of the time, it's
on the sides,
on the couch. Like, I don't even have it in. I own it very quickly kinds of put
it in like the
clothes that I wear on my neck is or something if they say, Oh, like, can I see
it when it gets
fair that I'm like, Oh, yeah, I'm so let me show you and I'm quickly like
trying to maneuver it
because it's your face that they mainly want to see. So it is good as well. If
you are a little
bit shy and it's a little bit more motivating because I know a lot of girls don
't like strip
and unless they get tips. So this is also a very easy way to say tip me because
you can say,
Oh, make me wet, like, press the toy or give me a little buzz and I'll start
doing it. It's
easy. I say in that I'm more appealing saying that rather than, Oh, if you tip
me, I'll do this
because you don't really have to say tip. You can kind of just blow a buzz buzz
because they've
got the control. They can see that it's in. So you blow a buzz buzz me toy and
get me get one first
then and most of the time they say yeah. Can I ask a question? But I've got a
couple of these and
obviously I'm doing a wrong because I've got I have a like I'm in shock right
now because I've
got that app on me mask and I'm copying and pasting a link and sharing that in
into the chat
with with the clients in in private. So I can actually link the toys too. I don
't wear it.
Man, I've been doing it wrong and I've fucked them off because they thought
this is just messing
around and it's in and they have both three of the buzzy things and they just
started the
bottom at the day. Oh yeah, chocolate, brilliant. Well, that's actually the
last points of thinking
the tips and tricks, isn't it? So I do do that. So what you've done, I do do
that. If the clients
willing to stay on, obviously you'll know yourself. It's really annoying. If
they're constantly just
asking for the link is you've got to try and send it and I've got a MacBook as
well and copying and
pasting things is really hard for some reason on the laptop as well. Like it
takes a couple of
thoughts here, isn't it? It cuts out the the reds. I mean, it kind of takes you
from, you know,
this like hot experience. So just let me just do this. It's happens and
whatever. Yeah, yeah.
That's why it's helpful with the high-paying kind because if they're going to
stay on the call
anyway, like the type that talked to you before and after and stuff like that,
I do do it with them.
I mainly only do that if they ask them because I'll always try and get the tips
because even
though you'll, I'll end up making more money on a longer private if I send them
the link,
you still, I still personally, anyway, make more money if they're actually
content. Yeah. I really
like the sounds of that to be fair and you can can you control the level of
like the buzz because
the one that I used the most is the little, or did you, the most was the little
, um,
the little bullet-y one, you know, like in fact, I'm uncomfortable with that.
That one. Oh, yeah. Because it's, you know, it's the least effort, I think. Um,
and I sent a link to
some, to some fella, who wears a regular but you must, but it didn't think the
set. And he put it on
was like, it was crazy anyway. And it, it, it, it, it shot me across the room.
I don't, I don't
know. I'm gonna have to put that away for a while. Like, honest regards, it was
, it was, it was not fun.
So can I turn the settings down? Yeah. I normally do the low tips for the
lowest one. So they have
to keep tipping. So if they send one credit, it goes off for like a couple,
like a couple of five
seconds. Yeah. So the sends and loads of ones because the second they get me
reaction, it's gone.
So they're like, oh, and then the tipping again. So I do the low one for that
because yeah, it would
be really intense if it was the highest one. And the only after sends a credit,
I'd be shot across
to do as well as that. I was like, well, yeah, because it was just now, there
was never open
and down a mess and we're doing that. And he must have just gone. And I was
like, oh, you don't
crazy to put it away. Yeah. So I think there's the only, the only reason to do
that is to like send
a direct link or copy and paste the link is really for high paying clients, isn
't it? It's like a reward
for them for spending a lot of time with you. And yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah, I'm
glad you can, we can
get that sorted, Bailey, and hopefully give you a boost in a different way.
Earnings boost.
And you mentioned there about free. So yeah, you were saying that it's a good,
it's a good
tool to have in free. And it is an amazing tool to have in free. I never have a
free now because
I do stay in like for probably 20 minutes at a time. So every 20 minutes that I
have in free,
I at least get wanted from the love and so it's more motivating because we all
know free can be
exhausting, especially in long periods of time as well, especially if it's
quiet as well,
because you feel like you're saying, Hi, how are you? How can I make your night
better?
Hi, how are you? What do you offer? And you'd explain to yourself over and over
again,
and I can get really bored. I find it and it can get frustrating and it's easy
to like,
Oh, it's, I'm logging off. It's not worth it. But it's a lot more worth it when
even if it's
just a couple of credits, it's something I see as if free is quiet. I'll, I'll
get a couple of tips.
And I'll think, okay, well, I've got three credits now from the tips. I'll use
that and I'll pay to boost.
And I'll put the money in it that way. But honestly, I get a lot because weird
ly enough,
these, a lot of people, a lot of men and I've noticed this probably more so
over the past four
months when I've really put all of my effort into free because I wanted to try
this new thing to
a money and it worked. And they spend the last credit or sometimes singular
last credit on just
random girls in free. Sometimes they won't even say anything. They won't even
wait for you to
respond to it, they'll tip and they'll leave. So you kind of just make a face
for the other people
because I think they think, Oh, I've got two credits. I'll, I'll go and give it
to, I'll go and give
it to where or I'll go and do this. Because sometimes if they do stay in the
chat room, you see their
purple icon. So obviously, if someone's got credit to the purple, and you might
give more
attention to the people with purple credit, not realising that they've only
actually got one
credit in their accounts. They can't even afford to take you to private for a
minute or group,
like depends on how much they've got left for the minute. So they're just a
three loads of
essentially, they can't take you to a room unless they top up. But they
normally then spend the last
one or two credits on yet and you'll see their purple name in real time, Go
Gray, which is interesting,
so they're like, Oh, you've got now you've got no credits now and then normally
the guy will
sometimes they'll top up. But I make low like loads of tips in free. They do
normally just tip
the one in free. I have had a few high tipers in free, but that is rare. It's
normally just
the one that's why I've kept such a loud tip on. To be fair, that is just for
free or to probably
was at least put it at like three, rather than one credit. But I have noticed I
do get a lot of
extra in free. I actually got some today. I got it off as well. So I don't.
So let me come in once and show you out there to feel like it's just ones. I
don't know if it's
going to focus, but they're in free, as you can see, and it was in the morning
and I was getting a
couple of tips of someone's calling me. I know I got to show you if I am, if I
log those, I'll get
suspended now. Yeah, it's so so motivating for free. It makes me want to do it
and I never thought
I'd say this. If you would have asked me in my country, maybe two years ago,
and like I hated
free, I would only do it for maybe 10 minutes at a time and every single time
it put me off because
I thought no, it's not worth it. Even if I do get a call, I'd like I don't like
having to sit there,
but it is really motivating. And they don't get to see anything either. So you
don't even have to
sit there and wear it because it can get uncomfortable. I just normally have it
on the side of the couch
and then obviously when it's vibrating, I'll react to it. And then not normally
get to other
people being like, have you got silent in private? Like if I tip you and take
you to a private,
will I be able to hear it as well? And I'm like, yeah, yeah. So it's a bargain
and fuel as well to be
like, yeah, you get to see more of this in private. Yeah, and then they do
normally take you. So I
think Lovense and free go hands and hands. It's honestly it pays for itself.
They can be a bit
expensive. Anyone who's watching this as well on the chain of video, it might
put you off because
I think probably the cheapest one is probably around £70 still, which is a lot
of money, especially
if you know, but it honestly, it's one of the best investments you can get. I
think, and it really
does pay for itself so quickly. And you can get a comfortable one. It even
helps me because I've
got this one. So it's kind of like a nickel one. It even helps me if I'm not
feeling pussy play,
like I don't actually want to show back as you all have moments and days when I
think, like,
I don't want to get me bit so so I don't want to take me top off or whatever.
And it helps
because I can keep me knickers on or sometimes even shorter, like, and I just
poke this out.
It's not even improperly. I'll just kind of poke this out at the top of me
pants. And the second
DC that they want to buzz, and it's more your face. I've noticed that they are
more into the
reaction of your face. Most of them that they won't even ask me to take
anything off. So I do use it,
and especially for mummy perias and stuff as well, because I'll just keep it in
me knickers. And I
just say, I know I'm not taking them off. You can see the toys in and it's not
even in and it's
hiding the tampon string. So I also say it's really good because I get that a
lot. I get that
I am questioning a lot from people saying, oh, what do you do? You tell
everyone if you still
want to make money. And I already actually put this in all around. And I just
keep that. But that's
also helpful on that side. And for that as well. Thank you so much. It's so
good.
That's why I got that little one, because you can just tell it in your hands.
And you can
obviously feel the fabric, but if you're leaving on the couch or on the beds or
whatever,
the buzz quite strongly is empty. So you know, you're just blaggy. Yeah, good
habit of fake it. Yeah.
Yeah. And I guess it would also be good like thinking about people with
different common styles.
Like obviously you could use it in like a sub scenario, like someone's buzzing
you. Maybe they're
like rewarding you for doing certain things or whatever. But also as a Dom as
well, you could
use it. Couldn't you could to like give your sub a treat if they do something
good, you know.
So you like you could incorporate it into different role plays and stuff.
Definitely. Yeah, definitely. I've actually had a few where by accident, like
Amazon's came
or something while I've been on the call. And I've been like, I'm very sorry, I
've got to run to
the door and they haven't even sent me before that. And then because I've left
and they assume
that I've got the toy in and they think I'm talking to the Amazon man, they'll
be buzzing and buzzing
and buzzing and buzzing and thinking I'm supposed to be like, like what if I
said, okay, I'm going
to go and get changed. I've noticed I'll walk away. Like they can't even hear
me. I'll walk away from
the laptop and I think they think it's really sexy now. When that I'm somewhere
in the house,
like obviously getting buzzed and normally it's fell on the floor. Like when I
'm like, oh no,
trying to pick it up and pretend. But yeah, it's there's a few like weird like
weird different
ways that or amazing different ways I should say really that like it has helped
me because
even like that, like running to the doors I quick. I've earned like another
like 10 credits just
from answering the door because they've had a sexy thought just because I've
had it connected.
And it's so easy once you've set it up, it stays connected like it's constantly
there. You only
have to turn it on. So it's no extra time having to mess about with it or
anything. It is just always
there. And it's always a bargain until especially for obviously like people who
are like I know we
said before but people who are shy and wouldn't feel comfortable asking for
tips. So it's just a
really easy thing to talk about. It's like Dom also. Yeah, yeah, it's a really
easy way to ask
for tips or you're not even asking really. Just set it up so that you can get
tips. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, do you have any other questions ladies or anything you want to add
about your
experience with it? Yeah, can I ask a question? Yeah, of course. So I've got, I
've tried to set
it up like four or five times and it's just never worked. I don't know what I'm
doing wrong but
I've got my toy with me now. All right. So I can, can I set this up through my
phone? I use my
phone a lot when I'm on cam. Well, I've been on cam for ages but I'm starting
again. So can I sign
this up through this? I don't actually think you can on the phones from memory
because I did try and
have a look at that just because I was curious because I did think that I went
if I'm on holiday
or something, I work through my phone as well and it'd be very easy to pack. So
I was thinking this
myself. I couldn't see on any of the instructions with setup that would work
with a phone because
it's a lot of downloading things for Chrome or downloading something to add to
like an extension
on your laptop. So I don't actually think, I don't know if they've got phone
options because they have
got a lot of different toys on there. I'm wondering if they maybe have an
option to do it because
obviously the way social media and the internet and stuff and everything is
going. I think they
will do that at some point. I think it would be really good for them to do that
but as of now,
I'm not sure if they have got anything that does work on the phone. I've had it
on the app
but I've never connected it to AdultWork. I've just struggled with it. So
where do I find that
step by step guy? Is that on AdultWork then? There's one on AdultWork and if
you make a
love-ins account or you might even order to have one if you've got the app, log
in to it like on
whatever you use like say Safari or Chrome type in like www.lovents and login
and then once you've
logged in, you can find AdultWork on love-ins and then once you've done that,
you can click stream
and it should take you to AdultWork as well. Do it, do it, do it, do it, do it
, do it, do it.
I'll have to add it to an extension because even mine here, especially yet, it
says extension
settings so that's how I got on that page to like edit all of my things and
that's my account
because I'm logged in to it because I'm prepared to be logged in to it now but
I have to add the
extension here like permanently there now but that wasn't there when I
initially settled but then
once it's there, even if this little green box does disappear, it's very rare
but it has happened
to me a few times, you can just click this and get it back. Okay perfect, I'll
give it another
goal then. I'll send you that, I'll send you that link to the integrations
stuff so you can have
a look at it either. Thank you, I'll give it another goal. Can I ask that to
please? Yeah of course,
yeah maybe I'll put it in the chat after this. Yeah, I think can I record you
doing a little
a little busy, I'll just step by step it's kind of the thing because I'll fuck
that race up me so
Yeah it is, it's honestly when I was setting it off, it was because I didn't
realise that
as it work has us because this was ages ago, I didn't realise that as it work
has as much
information as it was and I didn't realise I needed an account, I was like what
, what is this
house was there because there seems to be loads of steps but once you actually
find the instructions
it is actually quite easy to do, it's just a lot really, it's easy but there is
a few steps but then
once it's there it's always there then like even my little green box it just it
just stays there
so if I switch my toy off that should go, yeah so that then goes red but that
box should always
be there and then when you switch your back on it'll just connect and it'll go
back green
so that that is how easy it is and if for whatever reason it doesn't a little
trick is
because you'll get the app on your phone regardless, if you do this and just
scan the QR code it
connects straight away, well it turns green straight away. Okay another
question you know
what do they see on their screen, like can they see any of like your
information, like your name,
your email address or anything like that? Now from what I'm aware of and this
is just for me asking
me regulars because I'm curious, it's just like a remote control so they seem
to see
kinds of similar to that extension that are showing you but a smaller version
where it's like if you
tip one to four credits like for mine anyway it'll buzz for five minutes and
they have the controls
and they've got the control like to block and stuff and we've also got a
similar option to be fair
on this so I can't slip on each screen, I think it's something like this for
them but obviously
without that so they can kind of have a few different options but that'll it'll
be obviously
different because this is for me who's got it but that it's kind of similar so
somewhere on
their screen while you're live like this and you can click the different
options, you can also test
tip just to make sure that it is connected and obviously as you can hear it's
vibrating and so
that's also good to do because sometimes for some reason I have noticed that it
doesn't connect properly
and it's awkward when you're using sounds and descend the tip and then you can
't have to be
mowed louder because it's not actually vibrating and so trying to mask it real
old yeah and so
as always just test the tip if you're on for a couple of hours like if I'm
gonna be on like for
four hours say maybe like twice I'll just make sure that it is still working
and I'll just test
the tip as well. I've got one more question okay you know obviously I've
created a new account now
because of what happened previously so I wear a mask on cam now I've got
various different masks
would you recommend that I use more white like noises then rather because they
won't be able to
see my face or maybe would would you suggest like exaggerating noises making
more sexy moves that way
yeah 100% that's normally what that I feel like when I say face I don't even
really mean like
yeah actual facial features it is more of the noise the shock of it because
they normally
say something sick because I am very dramatic because I'm like like in it like
even if I'll just
be wearing something like that I'll be like oh my god that was the best thing
ever do that again
please please keep doing that and they're like whoa like that that gives you a
fright isn't it
does that woke you up haha how about this oh even better so yeah just exagger
ate anything like if
you are wearing a mask yeah if you can see your mouth though I think that would
still work
anything like this part covers in your mouth so even like like a big reaction
like that way
they'll love it like and the noise is obviously the noise is always help
everyone look one sounds
in private don't they so yeah thank you thank you oh thank you for the
questions they're really
helpful um anything else anything else that we might have missed Chloe
I'm trying to think about things so I think actually one thing is um if you've
got multiple
toys I don't know if you said that you've got a few baby you can connect more
than one at the
same time so I have only got the one toy so I don't know what that looks like
for the client but
um one of my girls has multiple toys and she was sharing me and her thing was
set up like
it was like lush too and then it was like a different one like lush seven and
it was all
there and they all had different settings and I thought that looked amazing and
I thought
obviously if you have got the money to do so and you do and you do end up
getting a few
because they do pay for themselves that would be really good I think that would
be
better because then you can give the clients the option because one thing I do
get with love
ends mainly in free is if you got another toy to use as well because it is a
vibrator and they all
want a dill so but you can get like dill so type love answers so that would be
good because you
could say with that question yeah but it's still a Lovense so they've
obviously still got to pay
for the pleasure of it going off and stuff so I think that would be that's
something I'm looking
to do really soon treat yourself Christmas I think I'm gonna invest in another
one and
so I can let everyone know when I do and see how that works for some of me
regulars but yeah I
think that's an even better way to play the conversation because it could just
have both got
one or anyone that does that one or is gonna get one you probably will see that
yourselves
especially in free that these who can't do to ask for other toys as well they
'll still tip
but they will suck hands and say okay like the credit to run and learn now or
what what else
if you go you could be like another Lovense do we know but are they all
connectable to
as well work like it doesn't matter what one you buy either all connectable or
no and one
just there and ones did you have that on the website though so if you go on
their website they
have got an adult like not as well as what work toys so it's a webcam section
but there's loads
of options on there but not every toy and because there was these knickers that
had a
vibration in the bottom of it and I thought that was amazing because I thought
you could
just wear that I won't even take them off like that's amazing but that wasn't
compatible with as well work or any streaming services so it's like okay thank
god I've read
that before the both of them so yeah only certain ones but they do have plenty
of options on there
from when I last seen yeah I bet that you'd do all the two that I've got are
compatible
let's have to say some of the couch here this is what you call the plan
oh thanks for that question that was a really good question yeah
yeah okay so is there any it's anything else Chloe you think that we've missed
I mean I think
that's there's a lot there's a lot in there I think it's been so useful
definitely definitely
I'm so glad that I ended up trying this because honestly I was hesitant in the
beginning because
I was making money anywhere and the art expenses and I thought is this going to
be a waste of time
like but on especially with free I just think they go hands and hands like I
won't go in free
now what I would say if this is theirs and it dies a lot because I've
constantly got it on for this
I won't do free until it's charged because I at least get two candidates every
single time I go in so
it is just anyone who needs motivation or is struggling a little bit because
there is more
competition than ever now with sex work there's constantly hundreds of pages
online it is really
a good investment and it will eventually pay for itself I think quite quickly
to be fair because
it's just so useful but yeah I'm so glad that's why I got them I got mine quite
early on and
obviously I've been doing it all wrong but I kind of on the trans girls page
there's there's never more
than like there's never more than one page well there is there's never more
than a hundred girls
on but there is a lot of girls who whose per minute is really fucking loud you
know what I mean
I think like sometimes that well definitely or the more strings see about it's
more inviting
isn't it you know what I mean yeah I said to cut these connectors and
and not blow myself a graph across the room yeah you're so right though like
because like
different people who are in different categories like I don't know housewives
or whatever category
you're in it's just it's just an extra thing like they're looking for a certain
type of person
and you've got a toy as well then yeah it gets quite niche doesn't it yeah
because all well I would
say like 80% to my cause is like girlfriend experience where we're going to go
what we're going to do
when we get home to the hotel blah blah blah blah blah blah and the most same
story 58 times
it's easy body
so bored and sometimes as well like I actually would rather be doing stuff
I'm like oh my god yeah normally type like that so it's so long which is so
good
which is because you're animal money but I'm like look at that it's like oh my
gosh
sometimes painful isn't it but yeah thing out of shot so you can yawn for a
moment
actually a lot of times on stage you want to see me tits so I'm like on Sunday
I did my
boring man it's probably like over sharing a bit of typing like it's slower
than I was typing
which is like on it ends up and just completely boring and I've gone to him so
do you want to
see me test Stuart should take me because I just so cause it interests me self
like fuck it
I wasn't I just the snowball on the call just like 40 minutes of him going yeah
fair play fair
play at me what the fuck does that even mean I am like that I'm exactly like
you like that on
my oh my gosh I hate it when um did you just put nice full stop and if if I
ever say a rarer
M's again in my life and blow me self off sutt and I'm like please come and mix
it off
now you can mix it off with your toys yeah and get like capital M's in a row
what was your turn back to the hotel I don't know what slides I was if you buzz
ed me toy yeah
it's a method and so that's thought if you took me 20 seconds
one last tip actually I was always put in the closet on I know a lot of the
girls do that with
the actual places you know like 299 I would do that's why I've got 16 because I
feel like I had
15 at one point and no one would ever send me 15 credits for some reason but
then when I changed
it to 16 and I can't remember the reason and why I did that but I know that
then became my most
popular tip because I think they think it's like a deal on 20 it's not but I
think that like you
know there's like a reason when they see that and think oh yeah that seems
lower than what it
actually is so that is something I do as well like I do it even if you don't
want to do one
singular credit because if you think oh like I can't be bothered to want one
credit I'd
do something like two or three like not five I'd either do a number below five
or a number
slightly over like six or something because I have notes just when I play about
with the
places like that I do get more tips and obviously 16 is a lot as well so I've
kept that one that's
like me meeting monks I'm like yeah I like that one yeah oh thank you so much
Chloe it's been so
useful it's been so good yeah yeah it's been great and I'll post the links and
stuff that we've got
into the chat if anybody wants to have a look and obviously like messages if
you need any help or
speechly mentor yeah one can message me or any of us we can all send everyone
in the right
direction but yeah and I'd want to know everybody's time on there and who's
tipping and how does it
then if you're getting some arguments and groups and stuff like I love to think
motivating I love
I love it I love it I love it so yeah yeah please let us know how you get on I
'd love to hear how you get
on I will say I might need some help so I'm not connected to next door's
microwave or something
but oh it's lovely to see you lovely to see you ladies I hope you do well if
you're going on tonight
and yeah I'll see you all soon thank you so much Chloe